A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Chancellor of the Virginia Community College System, 1964-2012
Library of Virginia
- Series II: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 31216], 1974-1980., Extent: 30 cu. ft. (30 boxes). (Box 1-30)
  - Management Information System, 1976 (Box 23)
  - Management Information System, Study (Box 23)
  - Memorandum, Vice-Chancellor's, 1974 (Box 23)
  - Minority Business Enterprise, Virginia State Office of (Box 23)
  - Minority Business Enterprise, Virginia State Office of, 1975 (Box 23)
  - Motor Vehicles, Division of (Box 23)
  - National Center for Higher Education Management Systems (Box 23)
  - National Center for Higher Education Management Systems (Box 23)
  - National Commission on Accrediting (Box 23)
  - National Council of State Directors (Box 23)
  - National Council of State Directors, Self Study (Box 23)
  - National Education Association (Box 23)
  - NLHE (National Laboratory for Higher Education) (Box 23)
  - National Invitation Conference on Institutional Eligibility (Box 23)
  - Nationally recognized accrediting agencies and associations (Box 24)
  - National Council of State Directors (Box 24)
  - National Retail Merchants Association (Box 24)
  - National Secretaries Association (Box 24)
  - Newspapers (Box 24)
  - Newspapers (Box 24)
  - Newspapers (Box 24)
  - Norfolk State College (Box 24)
  - North Carolina publications (Box 24)
  - NOVA University (Box 24)
  - Nuclear Medicine Technologists (Box 24)
  - Nursing, State Board of (Box 24)
  - O, Miscellaneous (Box 24)
  - Occupational Technical Coordinator (Box 24)
  - Off-campus courses (Box 24)
  - Off-campus locations (Box 24)
  - Office space (Box 24)
  - Ohio State University (Box 24)
  - Open admissions (Box 24)
  - Organizational chart, Single campus (Box 24)
  - Organizational memberships (Box 24)
  - Orientation sessions, New faculty (Box 24)
  - Oncken, William, Presents Managing Management Time (Box 24)
  - Papers by the Chancellor (Box 24)
  - Paralegal assistants (Box 24)
  - Para-professional (Box 24)
  - Paschall, Dr. David Y., Consultant (Box 24)
  - Peace Corps (Box 24)
  - Penn State University, Dept. of Vocational Education (Box 24)
  - Personnel Office, 1974-1976 (Box 24)
  - Personnel Office, 1975 (Box 24)
  - Personnel Office, 1977-1978 (Box 24)
  - Personnel Office, Payroll Study Committee (Box 24)
  - Personnel Office, Staffing rates (Box 24)
  - Personel Communique (Box 24)
  - Physical Education Facilities (Box 24)
  - Planning Districts (Box 24)
  - Planning for Higher Education (Box 24)
  - Police, Capitol (Box 24)
  - Police Science Programs (Box 24)
  - Policy, Professional Employees Appointment (Box 24)
  - Policy, Political Activities (Box 24)
  - Portland State University (Box 24)
  - Positions, Freeze on new (Box 24)
  - Post High School Education (Box 24)
  - Post secondary Education Advisory Committee (Box 24)
  - Presidents, VCCS memos, 1977 (Box 25)
  - Presidents, VCCS memos, 1977 (Box 25)
  - Presidents, VCCS memos, 1978 (Box 25)
  - Presidents, VCCS memos, 1978 (Box 25)
  - Presidents, VCCS memos, 1978 (Box 25)
  - Presidents, VCCS memos, 1978 (Box 25)
  - Presidents conference call (Box 25)
  - Presidents, Council of, 1974 (Box 25)
  - Presidents, Council of, 1974 (Box 25)
  - Presidents, Council of, 1974 (Box 25)
  - Presidential salaries, Evaluation (Box 25)
  - Presidential Candidates, Procedures for appointment (Box 25)
  - Plan for Equal Opportunity in Virginia Institutions of Higher Education (Box 25)
  - Professional Advisory Committee, 1974 (Box 25)
  - Professional Advisory Committee, 1974 (Box 25)
  - Professional Advisory Committee, 1974 (Box 25)
  - Professional Advisory Committee, 1975 (Box 25)
  - Professional Advisory Committee, 1976 (Box 25)
  - Professional Advisory Committee, Responses (Box 25)
  - Publications (Box 25)
  - Q, Miscellaneous (Box 25)
  - Report to top management (Box 25)
  - Representatives, House of, 1975 (Box 25)
  - Request related to positions (Box 25)
  - Requisitions, Maintenance and Operation Capital Outlay (Box 25)
  - Research, 1974 (Box 25)
  - Research activities, 1975 (Box 25)
  - Research and Planning, 1975 (Box 25)
  - Retail Merchants Advisory Committee (Box 26)
  - Roanoke COllege (Box 26)
  - R.T.I. (Box 26)
  - S, Miscellaneous (Box 26)
  - Salaries (Box 26)
  - Senate (Box 26)
  - Senior Citizen Centers (Box 26)
  - SACS (Southern Association of Colleges and Schools), Booklets and brochures (Box 26)
  - SACS, Correspondence, 1974 (Box 26)
  - SACS, Correspondence, 1974 (Box 26)
  - SACS, Correspondence, 1975 (Box 26)
  - SACS, Ad Hoc Committee, 1974 (Box 26)
  - SACS, Seminar, 1974 (Box 26)
  - SACS, Executive Council Meeting, 1974 (Box 26)
  - SACS, Annual meeting, 1974 (Box 26)
  - SACS, Conference, 1975 (Box 26)
  - SACS, Annual meeting, 1975 (Box 26)
  - SACS, AIES meeting, 1975 (Box 26)
  - Southern Growth Policies Board (Box 27)
  - Special Training (Box 27)
  - SCHEV, Health Professions and Occupation Committee (Box 27)
  - SCHEV, Health Professions and Occupation Committee meeting, 1974 April (Box 27)
  - SCHEV, Health Professions and Occupation Committee meeting, 1974 May (Box 27)
  - SCHEV, Health Professions and Occupation Committee meeting, 1974 November (Box 27)
  - SCHEV, Health Professions and Occupation Committee meeting, 1975 April (Box 27)
  - SCHEV, Health Professions and Occupation Committee meeting, 1975 July (Box 27)
  - SCHEV, Health Professions and Occupation Committee, Allied Health Manpower Report (Box 27)
  - SCHEV, Health Professions and Occupation Committee, Policies and Procedures (Box 27)
  - SCHEV, Health Professions and Occupation Committee meeting, 1976 March (Box 27)
  - SCHEV, Health Professions and Occupation Committee meeting, 1976 June (Box 27)
  - SCHEV, Health Professions and Occupation Committee meeting, 1976 October (Box 27)
  - SCHEV, Health Professions and Occupation Committee meeting, 1976 November (Box 27)
  - SCHEV, Health Professions and Occupation Committee meeting, 1977 January (Box 27)
  - SCHEV, Health Professions and Occupation Committee, Graduate Education (Box 27)
  - SCHEV, Health Professions and Occupation Committee,, Medical technology program proposal (Box 27)
  - SCHEV, Health Professions and Occupation Committee, Gerontology program (Box 27)
  - SCHEV, Health Professions and Occupation Committee, Doctor of pharmacy program proposal (Box 27)
  - SCHEV, Health Professions and Occupation Committee, Serving the Aging (Box 27)
  - SCHEV, Health Professions and Occupation Committee, Norfolk State College (Box 27)
  - SCHEV, Institutional Changes, 1974 (Box 27)
  - SCHEV, Correspondence (Box 27)
  - SCHEV, Committees (Box 28)
  - SCHEV, Enrollment projections (Box 28)
  - SCHEV, Publications (Box 28)
  - SCHEV, Publications (Box 28)
  - SCHEV, Publications (Box 28)
  - SCHEV, Executive Officers Association (Box 28)
  - Space Planning Guidelines (Box 28)
  - Speech, Chester Masonic Lodge, 1975 (Box 28)
  - Speech, Downtown Businessmen's luncheon, 1975 (Box 28)
  - Speech, Council on Specialized Accrediting Agencies, 1975 (Box 28)
  - Speech, Friends of the Industry of Agriculture, 1975 (Box 28)
  - Speech, Fort Eustis, 1975 (Box 28)
  - Speech, Edward Lane, 1975 (Box 28)
  - Speech, Phi Delta Kappa, 1974 (Box 28)
  - Speech information, 1974-1975 (Box 28)
  - Speech, VPI, 1975 (Box 28)
  - Speech, Duke University, 1974 (Box 28)
  - Speech, Joppa Masonic Lodge, 1975 (Box 28)
  - Speech, Kiwanis Club, 1975 (Box 28)
  - Speech, State Agency Head Wives, 1975 (Box 28)
  - Speech, Virginia Council on State Legislation, 1975 (Box 28)
  - Speech, Senator Walker, 1975 (Box 28)
  - Speech, Edward E. Willey, 1975 (Box 28)
  - Speech, Wise County Youth Council, 1975 (Box 28)
  - Staff folder (Box 28)
  - Staff folder, Special Training (Box 28)
  - Staff folder, Educational Programs (Box 28)
  - Staff folder, Research and Planning (Box 28)
  - Staff folder, Management Services (Box 28)
  - Student Services Meeting, 1973 (Box 28)
  - State Agency Luncheon, 1974 (Box 28)
  - State Fire Marshall, 1976 (Box 28)
  - State Government Management, Commission on, 1974 (Box 28)
  - Student Rights (Box 28)
  - T (Box 29)
  - Taxation, Dept. of (Box 29)
  - Technical and Comprehensive Education (Box 29)
  - Tenure Study (Box 29)
  - Tenure (Box 29)
  - Testing, CGP Elimination (Box 29)
  - Thank You's (Box 29)
  - Training and Standards Commission (Box 29)
  - Tuition, VCC System (Box 29)
  - Tuition (Box 29)
  - Twelve O Two Commission (Box 29)
  - US Foreign Policy and National Security Seminar (Box 29)
  - Unions (Box 29)
  - University of Richmond (Box 29)
  - University of Florida (Box 29)
  - University of Michigan (Box 29)
  - University of North Carolina (Box 29)
  - University of Virginia (Box 29)
  - University of Virginia, Clinch Valley College (Box 29)
  - Virginia Council of Churches (Box 29)
  - VCU, Dentistry (Box 29)
  - Veterans Administration (Box 29)
  - Veterans, Standards of Progress (Box 29)
  - Virginia Agribusiness Council (Box 29)
  - Virginia Association of Surveyors (Box 29)
  - Virginia Advisory Council (Box 29)
  - Virginia Council for the Deaf (Box 29)
  - VCC System (Box 29)
  - Virginia Plan for Higher Education (Box 29)
  - VMI (Virginia Military Institute) (Box 29)
  - Virginia College Scholarship Assistance Program (Box 29)
  - Virginia Municipal League (Box 29)
  - Virginia Social Science Association (Box 29)
  - Virginia Association of Community and Junior Colleges (Box 29)
  - Virginia State Board of Veterinarian Examiners (Box 29)
  - Virginia State College (Box 29)
  - Vocational Education, State Advisory Council on, 1974-1976 (Box 30)
  - Vocational Education, Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 30)
  - VPI and SU (Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University), 1974-1976 (Box 30)
  - Volunteerism, State Office on, 1975-1976 (Box 30)
  - William and Mary, College of, 1974-1976 (Box 30)
  - WTVR TV (Box 30)
  - Water Control Board (Box 30)
- Series III: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 43207], 1990-2003., Extent: 12 cu. ft. (12 boxes). (Box 1-12)
  - 1991 January - June (Box 1)
  - 1991 July - December (Box 1)
  - 1992 January - June (Box 1)
  - 1992 July - September (Box 1)
  - 1992 October - December (Box 1)
  - 1993 January - May (Box 2)
  - 1993 June - August (Box 2)
  - 1993 September - October (Box 2)
  - 1993 November - December (Box 2)
  - 1994 January - February (Box 2)
  - 1994 March - April (Box 3)
  - 1994 May - June (Box 3)
  - 1994 July - August (Box 3)
  - 1994 September - October (Box 4)
  - 1994 November - December (Box 4)
  - 1995 January - February (Box 4)
  - 1995 March - April (Box 4)
  - 1995 May - June (Box 4)
  - 1995 July - August (Box 4)
  - 1995 September - October (Box 5)
  - 1995 November - December (Box 5)
  - 1996 January - February (Box 5)
  - 1996 March - April (Box 5)
  - 1996 May - June (Box 5)
  - 1996 July - August (Box 5)
  - 1996 September - October (Box 6)
  - 1996 November - December (Box 6)
  - 1997 January - February (Box 6)
  - 1997 March - April (Box 6)
  - 1997 May - June (Box 6)
  - 1997 August (Box 6)
  - 1997 September - October (Box 7)
  - 1997 November - December (Box 7)
  - 1998 January - February (Box 7)
  - 1998 March - April (Box 7)
  - 1998 May - June (Box 7)
  - 1998 July - August (Box 7)
  - 1998 September - October (Box 8)
  - 1998 November - December (Box 8)
  - 1999 January - February (Box 8)
  - 1999 March - April (Box 8)
  - 1999 May - June (Box 8)
  - 1999 July - August (Box 8)
  - 1999 September - October (Box 8)
  - 1999 November - December (Box 8)
  - 2000 January - February (Box 8)
  - 2000 March - April (Box 8)
  - 2000 May - June (Box 9)
  - 2000 July - August (Box 9)
  - 2000 September - October (Box 9)
  - 2000 November - December (Box 9)
  - 2001 January - February (Box 9)
  - 2001 March - April (Box 9)
  - 2001 May - June (Box 9)
  - 2001 July - August (Box 9)
  - 2001 September - October (Box 9)
  - 2001 November - December (Box 10)
  - 2002 January - February (Box 10)
  - 2002 March - April (Box 10)
  - 2002 May - June (Box 10)
  - 2002 July - August (Box 10)
  - 2002 September - October (Box 10)
  - 2002 November - December (Box 10)
  - 2003 January - February (Box 10)
  - 2003 March - April (Box 10)
  - Presidents Memorandum, 1990-1991 (Box 11)
  - Presidents Memorandum, 2000 (Box 11)
  - Presidents Memorandum, 2001 (Box 11)
  - Public Affairs, Assistant Chancellor, 2001 (Box 11)
  - Residents Enrolled in Virginia Institutions of Higher Education, By Locale (Box 11)
  - Transformational Leadership Qualities in Distance Education Leaders, Dissertation (Box 11)
  - Virginia Workforce Council Briefing Book (Box 11)
  - Governor's Commission on Champion Schools (Box 11)
  - Annual meeting, 1989 (Box 12)
  - Annual meeting 1990 (Box 12)
  - Annual meeting, 1993 (Box 12)
  - Thomas Nelson Community College, Report, Employer Scan Results, 1999 (Box 12)
  - Thomas Nelson Community College, Report, Public Perception and Awareness, 1999 (Box 12)
  - Thomas Nelson Community College, Report, Student Satisfaction Study, 1999 (Box 12)
  - VCCS, Data Processing, Semester paper by N. Kent Rockwell, 1992 (Box 12)
  - George Mason University, Report, Faculty Efforts to Keep Up with New Developments in Their Teaching Fields, 1992 (Box 12)
- Series IV: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 43865], 1970-2003 [bulk 1995-2001]., Extent: 13 cu. ft. (13 boxes). (Box 1-13)
  - Blue Ridge Community College, Misc., 2000 (Box 1)
  - Blue Ridge Community College, President's Office, 2000 (Box 1)
  - Blue Ridge Community College, President's Office, 2001 (Box 1)
  - Central Virginia Community College, College Board Minutes, 2001 (Box 1)
  - Central Virginia Community College, Misc., 2000 (Box 1)
  - Central Virginia Community College, President's Office, 2000 (Box 1)
  - Central Virginia Community College, Misc., 2001 (Box 1)
  - Central Virginia Community College, President's Office, 2001 (Box 1)
  - Dabney S. Lancaster Community College, President's Office, 2000 (Box 1)
  - Dabney S. Lancaster Community College, College Board Minutes, 2000 (Box 1)
  - Dabney S. Lancaster Community College, President's Office, 2001 (Box 1)
  - Danville Community College, Misc., 2000 (Box 1)
  - Danville Community College, President's Office, 2000 (Box 1)
  - Danville Community College, President's Office, 2001 (Box 1)
  - Eastern Shore Community College, President's Office, 2000 (Box 1)
  - Eastern Shore Community College, Misc., 2001 (Box 1)
  - Eastern Shore Community College, President's Office, 2001 (Box 1)
  - Germanna Community College, President's Office, 2000 (Box 1)
  - Germanna Community College, Misc., 2001 (Box 1)
  - Germanna Community College, President's Office, 2001 (Box 1)
  - J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College, Misc., 2000 (Box 1)
  - J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College, President's Office, 2000 (Box 1)
  - J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College, Misc., 2001 (Box 1)
  - J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College, President's Office, 2001 (Box 1)
  - John Tyler Community College, Misc., 2000 (Box 2)
  - John Tyler Community College, President's Office, 2000 (Box 2)
  - John Tyler Community College, Misc., 2001 (Box 2)
  - John Tyler Community College, President's Office, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Lord Fairfax Community College, President's Office, 2000 (Box 2)
  - Lord Fairfax Community College, President's Office, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Mountain Empire Community College, Misc., 2000 (Box 2)
  - Mountain Empire Community College, President's Office, 2000 (Box 2)
  - Mountain Empire Community College, Misc., 2001 (Box 2)
  - Mountain Empire Community College, President's Office, 2001 (Box 2)
  - New River Community College, Misc., 2000 (Box 2)
  - New River Community College, President's Office, 2000 (Box 2)
  - New River Community College, Misc., 2001 (Box 2)
  - New River Community College, President's Office, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Northern Virginia Community College, Misc., 2000 (Box 2)
  - Northern Virginia Community College, President's Office, 2000 (Box 2)
  - Northern Virginia Community College, Misc., 2001 (Box 2)
  - Northern Virginia Community College, President's Office, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Patrick Henry Community College, Misc., 2000 (Box 2)
  - Patrick Henry Community College, President's Office, 2000 (Box 2)
  - Patrick Henry Community College, Misc., 2001 (Box 2)
  - Patrick Henry Community College, President's Office, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Paul D. Camp Community College, President's Office, 2000 (Box 2)
  - Paul D. Camp Community College, Misc., 2001 (Box 2)
  - Paul D. Camp Community College, President's Office, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Piedmont Virginia Community College, President's Office, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Piedmont Virginia Community College, Misc., 2001 (Box 3)
  - Piedmont Virginia Community College, President's Office, 2001 (Box 3)
  - Rappahannock Community College, Misc., 2000 (Box 3)
  - Rappahannock Community College, President's Office, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Rappahannock Community College, Misc., 2001 (Box 3)
  - Rappahannock Community College, President's Office, 2001 (Box 3)
  - Southside Virginia Community College, Misc., 2000 (Box 3)
  - Southside Virginia Community College, President's Office, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Southside Virginia Community College, President's Office, 2001 (Box 3)
  - Southwest Virginia Community College, President's Office, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Southwest Virginia Community College, President's Office, 2001 (Box 3)
  - Thomas Nelson Community College, Misc., 2000 (Box 3)
  - Thomas Nelson Community College, President's Office, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Thomas Nelson Community College, Misc., 2001 (Box 3)
  - Thomas Nelson Community College, President's Office, 2001 (Box 3)
  - Tidewater Community College, Misc., 2000 (Box 3)
  - Tidewater Community College, President's Office, 2001 (Box 3)
  - Tidewater Community College, Relocation of Portsmouth Campus, 2000- 2001 (Box 3)
  - Tidewater Community College Community College, President's Office, 2000 (Box 4)
  - Virginia Highlands Community College, Misc., 2000 (Box 4)
  - Virginia Highlands Community College, President's Office, 2000 (Box 4)
  - Virginia Highlands Community College, President's Office, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Virginia Western Community College, Misc., 2000 (Box 4)
  - Virginia Western Community College, Meeting with Wytheville Local Board, 2000 (Box 4)
  - Virginia Western Community College, President's Office, 2000 (Box 4)
  - Virginia Western Community College, Misc., 2001 (Box 4)
  - Virginia Western Community College, Presidential search, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Virginia Western Community College, President's Office, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Wytheville Community College, Misc., 2000 (Box 4)
  - Wytheville Community College, President's Office, 2000 (Box 4)
  - Wytheville Community College, President's Office, 2001 (Box 4)
  - GPAC (General Professional Advisory Committee), 2000 (Box 4)
  - GPAC (General Professional Advisory Committee), 2001 (Box 4)
  - APOC (Advisory Council of Presidents) meetings, Minutes, 1999 August 3-4 (Box 5)
  - APOC (Advisory Council of Presidents) meetings, Minutes, 1999 October 5-6 (Box 5)
  - APOC (Advisory Council of Presidents) meetings, Minutes, 1999 November 30 - December 1 (Box 5)
  - APOC (Advisory Council of Presidents) meetings, Minutes, 2000 February 1-2 (Box 5)
  - APOC (Advisory Council of Presidents) meetings, Minutes, 2000 April 4-5 (Box 5)
  - APOC (Advisory Council of Presidents) meetings, Minutes, 2000 June 13-14 (Box 5)
  - APOC (Advisory Council of Presidents) meetings, Minutes, 2000 August 8-9 (Box 6)
  - APOC (Advisory Council of Presidents) meetings, Minutes, 2000 October 10-11 (Box 6)
  - APOC (Advisory Council of Presidents) meetings, Minutes, 2000 December 12-13 (Box 6)
  - APOC (Advisory Council of Presidents) meetings, Minutes, 2001 February 13-14 (Box 6)
  - APOC (Advisory Council of Presidents) meetings, Minutes, 2001 April 18 (Box 6)
  - APOC (Advisory Council of Presidents) meetings, Minutes, 2001 June 12-13 (Box 6)
  - APOC (Advisory Council of Presidents) meetings, Minutes, 2001 August 21-22 (Box 6)
  - APOC (Advisory Council of Presidents) meetings, Minutes, 2001 October 16-17 (Box 6)
  - APOC (Advisory Council of Presidents) meetings, Minutes, 2001 December 4-5 (Box 6)
  - APOC (Advisory Council of Presidents) meetings, Minutes, 2002 February 19-20 (Box 7)
  - APOC (Advisory Council of Presidents) meetings, Minutes, 2002 April 16-17 (Box 7)
  - APOC (Advisory Council of Presidents) meetings, Minutes, 2002 June 18-19 (Box 7)
  - APOC (Advisory Council of Presidents) meetings, Minutes, 2002 August 27-28 (Box 7)
  - APOC (Advisory Council of Presidents) meetings, Minutes, 2002 October 3-4 (Box 7)
  - APOC (Advisory Council of Presidents) meetings, Minutes, 2002 December 17-18 (Box 7)
  - APOC (Advisory Council of Presidents) meetings, Minutes, 2003 February 18-19 (Box 7)
  - APOC (Advisory Council of Presidents) meetings, Minutes, 2003 April 15-16 (Box 7)
  - APOC (Advisory Council of Presidents) meetings, Minutes, 2003 June 24-25 (Box 7)
  - APOC (Advisory Council of Presidents) meetings, Minutes, 2003 August 26-27 (Box 7)
  - APOC (Advisory Council of Presidents) meetings, Minutes, 2003 October 2-3 (Box 7)
  - APOC (Advisory Council of Presidents) meetings, Minutes, 2003 December 16-17 (Box 7)
  - Chancellor's Faculty Advisory meetings, Minutes, 1999 November 4-5 (Box 8)
  - Chancellor's Faculty Advisory meetings, Minutes, 2000 March 30-31 (Box 8)
  - Chancellor's Faculty Advisory meetings, Minutes, 2000 November 2-3 (Box 8)
  - Chancellor's Faculty Advisory meetings, Minutes, 2001 February 22-23 (Box 8)
  - Chancellor's Faculty Advisory meetings, Minutes, 2001 November 8-9 (Box 8)
  - Chancellor's Faculty Advisory meetings, Minutes, 2002 April 11-12 (Box 8)
  - Chancellor's Faculty Advisory meetings, Minutes, 2002 November 7-8 (Box 8)
  - Chancellor's Faculty Advisory meetings, Minutes, 2003 November 13-14 (Box 8)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV), 2001 (Box 8)
  - Council of Presidents meetings, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Council of Presidents meetings, 2001 (Box 8)
  - APOC (Advisory Council of Presidents) meetings, Minutes, 1998 February 3-4 (Box 9)
  - APOC (Advisory Council of Presidents) meetings, Minutes, 1998 April 7-8 (Box 9)
  - APOC (Advisory Council of Presidents) meetings, Minutes, 1998 May 26-27 (Box 9)
  - APOC (Advisory Council of Presidents) meetings, Minutes, 1998 August 4-5 (Box 9)
  - APOC (Advisory Council of Presidents) meetings, Minutes, 1998 October 6-7 (Box 9)
  - APOC (Advisory Council of Presidents) meetings, Minutes, 1998 December 1-2 (Box 9)
  - APOC (Advisory Council of Presidents) meetings, Minutes, 1999 January 12 (Box 10)
  - APOC (Advisory Council of Presidents) meetings, Minutes, 1999 February 2-3 (Box 10)
  - APOC (Advisory Council of Presidents) meetings, Minutes, 1999 April 13-14 (Box 10)
  - Chancellor's Faculty Advisory meetings, Minutes, 1998 November 5-6 (Box 10)
  - Chancellor's Faculty Advisory meetings, Minutes, 1999 March 29-30 (Box 10)
  - Blue Ridge Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Central Virginia Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Dabney S. Lancaster Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Danville Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Eastern Shore Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Germanna Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - John Tyler Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Lord Fairfax Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Mountain Empire Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - New River Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Northern Virginia Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Patrick Henry Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Paul D. Camp Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Piedmont Virginia Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Rappahannock Community College, 2002 (Box 10)
  - Southside Virginia Community College, 2002 (Box 10)